Guide to the Women's Fund for Health Education and Resiliency (HER) Records 2000-002
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
- Granting Process, 1980-2011
  - Grant Applications and Processing, 1980-2011
    - In Kind Formation, 2008; 2010 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Development – Raffle Information, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Fund Grants History, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Donation Policies, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Donor Appreciation Events (invitations & awards), undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Cardiovascular Health in Women – Project Donors, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Gant Writer's Network of Greater Houston, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Grant Eligibility, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Grants Funded Summaries, 1991-1994; 1997 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Grants, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Research Grants, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Grant History/ Recipients, 1991-1992; 1997 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Grant Applications, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Grants: Coalition for a Healthier Community (DHHS), 2010 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Grant Applications, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Grant Applications, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Grant Applications, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - C. Kent Osborne, M.D. –Baylor, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - C. Kent Osborne, M.D. –Baylor, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Rodney Appell, M.D., 2001-2003 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Catherine L. Troisi, Ph.D.-UT Health Science, 1999-2002 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Donna Przepiorka, M.D. PhD (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Lynn Young, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Katz, J. Lawrence, Ph.D. University of Texas, Health Science, 2000-2002 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Yu-Lee, Li-Yuan – Baylor College of Medicine, 2000-2002 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Hays, Jennifer Ph.D. –Baylor College of Medicine, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Khan, Firyal S. Ph.D. –The University of Texas Health Science Center, 2000-2002 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Heard, Michael J. M.D. –Baylor College of Medicine, 2000-2002 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Strobel, Henry W. Ph.D. –University of Texas Health Science, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Li-Yuan, Yu-Lee, Ph.D. – Baylor College of Medicine, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Janet E. Price, DVM, Ph.D. –MD Anderson, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Knowlton, Anne, M.D. –Baylor College of Medicine, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Changping Zou, M.D., Ph.D. –University of TX Health Science Center, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Heresi, Gloria, M.D. The University of TX Health Science Center, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Verschraegen, Claire, M.D. - MD Anderson Cancer Center, 1999-2001 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Lin-Yuan Yu-Lee, Ph.D. –Baylor College of Medicine, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Dorothy Weston, The Rose, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Hui Zheng, Ph.D. –Baylor College of Medicine, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Buck, David S. M.D. M.P.H.; Baylor College of Medicine, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Pre 2009 Research & Review Contracts Ducy, Patricia, Ph.D. –Baylor College of Medicine, 2000-2002 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Strobel, Henry W. –UT Health Science Center, 2001-2003 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Research and Review Committee, 1984-2008
    - Research and Review, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Research and Review, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Research and Review: Patricia Ducy, Et al., 2000 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Changping Zou, M.D. Ph.D. –The University of Texas Health Science Center, 1999-2001 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Research and Review; Richard W. Yee, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Research and Review; Dr. Michael A. Belford M.D., 1993 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Grant Contracts, 1985-1990 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Grant Proposal and Request for Funding for Publication of, A Primer on Women's Health, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Primer Records- Postage/ Stamps/ Returned Mail, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Research and Review; Grant Contracts, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Research and Review Committee -1994 Grants Awarded (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Research and Review Committee -1993 Grants Memorandums (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Research and Review Committee – Denied and Meritorious Proposals, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Research and Review Committee- Memorandum- 1994 Grant Summaries (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Research and Review Committee – Estrogen Replacement Therapy and Recurrence or Progression of Heart Disease in Post-Menopausal Women, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Research and Review Committee- Role of nitric oxide in the protective mechanism of estrogen-treated spontaneously hypertensive rats, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Research and Review Committee- Sixth Annual "Decade of the Brain" Symposium, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Research and Review Committee – "The Effect of Hormone Replacement Therapy on Metabolism of the Atherogenic Lipoprotein", 1996 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Research and Review –Interactive Women's Health Education & Disease Prevention Assessment Kiosk, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Research and Review Committee –Free Clinic for Women, "Living and Coping with Breast Cancer", 1996 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Research and Review Committee –The Role of TSC2 in Formation of Fibroids, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Research and Review Committee –Development of an Animal Model for Osteoporosis to Determine the Effect of NSAIDs on Post-Menopausal Bone Loss, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Research and Review Committee –Apolipoprotein E and Risk Factors for Coronary Heart Disease in Female Youth, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Research and Review Committee –A Group of Mutations in the Human Progesterone Gene as a Risk Indicator for Non-Familial Ovarian Cancer, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Research Grant –"Prolactin Receptor Involvement in Switching on Genes Involved in Breast Cancer", 1995 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Research Grant –Identification of a Molecular Fingerprint to Predict Metastases in Breast Cancer Patients, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Research Grant –Girls in Charge! Ensuring Healthy Development and Positive Lifestyle Choices for a Lifetime, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Research Grant –An Innovative Approach to the Treatment of Severe Obesity in Latina Adolescents, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Research Grant –Identification of Novel Biomarkers Associated with the Metabolic Syndrome & Prediabetes State in Obese Women by Genomics & Proteomics, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Research Grant –Endopelvic Fascia- Does Disruption Affect Results of Sling Surgery for Stress Urinary Incontinence?, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Research Grant –Estrogen Dependent Expression in Human Female-Specific Cythochrome P450 3A43 and Drug Response, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Research Grant –Female Hormones in Systemic Lupus Erythematosus: Gene Expression Profile, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Research Grant –Development of an In Vivo Model for Chemoprevention of Cervical Cancer and Suppression of Human Papillomavirus, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - "Your First Pelvic" – An Educational Videotape for Adolescents, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Research and Review Committee: The Incidence of H. Pylori Antibodies in People with Interstitial Cystitis, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Research and Review Committee: Climacteric Oophorectomy Accelerates Aging, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Research and Review Committee: Role of estrogen levels in treatment strategies for postmenopausal depression, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Research and Review Committee: "Role of Platelet-activating factor in breast cancer", 1993 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Research and Review Committee: Committee Formation –St. Luke's Episcopal Hospital, Texas Children's Hospital, Texas Heart Institute, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Research and Review Committee: "Hormonally-Responsive Proteins in the Human Reproductive Tract –Baylor College of Medicine, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Research and Review Committee: UT Healthy Science Center at Houston –Press Release, undated (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Research and Review Committee: Small Grants Applications- UT Medical School, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Research and Review Committee: Request for Research Grant –UT Healthy Science Center at Houston, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Research and Review Committee: Request for Research Grant – Corinthian House, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Research and Review Committee: Guidelines for Recommending Grants –Draft, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Research and Review Committee: Committee Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Research and Review Committee: Baylor College of Medicine Memorandum- Signing on the Committee, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Research and Review Committee: General Policy and Information for Grant Application, undated (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Research and Review Committee: The University of Texas Houston Health Science Center, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Research and Review Committee: HEB Grant Proposal, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Research and Review Committee: Baylor College of Medicine –Grants and Contracts: Financial Status Report, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Research and Review Committee: Breast Cancer and Thyroid Cancer in Women: an Epidemiologic Survey and Implications for Treatment, 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Research and Review Committee: Innovative Molecular Therapies for Vaccine Development in Ovarian Cancer, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Research and Review Committee: Support for the Programs of the Texas Women's Reproductive Health Consortium, 1998; 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Research and Review Committee: Research Papers, 1998; 2000 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Research and Review Committee: Discovery You! Lay Summary Report, 1999; 2001; 2003 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Research and Review Committee: Peggy B. Smith Ph.D., 1993; 1998 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Research and Review Committee: Ann Brinkeroff, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Research and Review Committee: Changping. Zou M.D., 2001 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Research and Review Committee: Health Care for the Homeless Annual Report, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Research and Review Committee: Anne A. Knowlton, M.D., 2004 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Research and Review Committee: Dr. William E. Findley, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Research and Review Committee: 1993 Contracts, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Research and Review Committee: Oral Immunization to Prevent Breast Cancer, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Research and Review Committee: Immunoregulatory Cytokine Changes during Normal Menstrual cycles in Asthmatic Women, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Research and Review Committee: Interactions between sex hormones and Retinoids in ovarian cancer cell lines, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Research and Review Committee: The Rose, Breast Health Education, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Research and Review Committee: The Rose, Breast Health Education, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Research and Review Committee: Genetics of Endometriosis, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Research and Review Committee: Autoimmune Mechanisms and Pathogenesis of Sjogren 's Syndrome (SS) and Graft-versus-host disease (GVHD), 1997 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Research and Review Committee: The Influence of Estrogen Replacement Therapy on Cerebral Atrophy among Patients with Dementias of the Vascular and Alzheimer's Types, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Research and Review Committee: Peritoneal fluid insulin growth factor binding protein levels in endometriosis compared to controls: before and after GNRHa (gonadotropin releasing hormone Agonist) treatment, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Research and Review Committee: Insulin-like Growth Factor Binding Protein in the Uterus and Peritoneal Cavity of women with Endometriosis, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Research and Review Committee: A Medical Education Program in Female Clinical Anatomy, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Research and Review Committee: Anti-Growth Action of a Monoclonal Antibody to Prolactin Receptor, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Research and Review Committee: Insulin sensitivity in premenstrual syndrome patients versus normal patients as measured by the minimal model of frequently sampled insulin glucose tolerance test, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Research and Review Committee: Proposal for Funding of Sponsorship of Provide Mammograms and Diagnostic Services for Medically Underserved Needy Women, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - Research and Review Committee: Nurturing the Professional Identity of Nurses, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - Research and Review Committee: Effects of Estrogen Replacement Therapy on Cerebral Blood Flow and Cognition, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Research and Review Committee: Oral Glucose Tolerance Test and The Preparatory Diet, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Research and Review Committee: Innovative Molecular Therapeutics for the Reversal of Drug Resistance in Breast Cancer, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Research and Review Committee: Women's Health Assessment Kiosk, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Research and Review Committee: Vascular Endothelial Growth Facor and Interleukin-6 levels among Oral Contraceptive users, Women taking Medroxyprogesterone Acetate and Women with Endometriosis, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Research and Review Committee: The Secretory Immune System and Breast Cancer, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Research and Review Committee: Training on Awareness and Assessment of Domestic Violence for Medical Professionals Working in Hospital and Clinic Settings, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Research and Review Committee: Examination of Mechanism That May Contribute to Premature, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Research and Review Committee: De Madres a Madres, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - Research and Review Committee: Examination of the Growth Hormone Axis in Menopausal and Lupron-Treated Women: Implications for Osteoporosis and Endometriosis Therapy, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Research and Review Committee: Compact Magnetic Resonance Imaging System for Breast Cancer Imaging, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - Research and Review Committee: Molecular Cloning of New Breast Cancer Regulatory Genes, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Research and Review Committee: Are women's Risk Factors for Cardiovascular Disease Being Identified and Treated?, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - Research and Review Committee: Proliferation rate and cJun CFos protooncogene expression in leiomyoma and adjacent normal myometrial smooth muscle cells, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Research and Review Committee: Proposal for Funding of Sponsorship Program for Medically Underserved Women, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Research and Review Committee: Evaluation of Obstetrical and newborn Characteristics by type of provider, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - Research and Review Committee: The Use of Deep Water Exercise Training in Osteoporotic Women, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Research and Review Committee: The Molecular Genetics of Predisposition of Carcinomas of the Breast and Associated Tumors, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 91)
    - Research and Review Committee: Factors Regulating Follicular Growth, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - Research and Review Committee: The Effects of Estrogen Replacement Therapy on Cardiac Structure and Function of Post-Menopausal Women, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 93)
    - Research and Review Committee: "Project Go-Getter", 1991 (Box 18, Folder 94)
    - Research and Review Committee: Educational Intervention into High-Risk Reproductive Behavior Among Inner City Adolescents, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - Research and Review Committee: Effects of Chlamydia and Mycoplasmas on Preimplantation Embryogenesis, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 96)
    - Research and Review Committee: Tear Duct Equipment –Hermann Eye Center, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 97)
    - Research and Review Committee: Acyclovir During The Last Four Weeks of Pregnancy in Patients with Recurrent Genital Herpes, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 98)
    - Research and Review Committee: Funding Proposal for Establishment of a Basic Science Laboratory and the Continuation of Previously Funded Work-Baylor College of Medicine, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 99)
    - Research and Review Committee: The Variations of Red Blood Cell Proton T1 and T2 Relaxation Times in Premenstrual Syndrome, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 100)
    - Research and Review Committee: Iatrogenic Gastroschisis Decreases Pulmonary Hypoplasia in an Ovine Congenital Diaphragmatic Hernia Model, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 101)
    - Research and Review Committee: The Effects of Pregnancy on the Vascular Reactivity of the Cerebral Blood Vessels in a Guinea Pig Model, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 102)
    - Research and Review Committee: Repetitive Responses to Clomiphene Citrate in Normal women of Late Reproductive Age, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 103)
    - Research and Review Committee: Regulation of the Corpus Luteum, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 104)
    - Research and Review Committee: The Relationship Between Adult Periodontitis and Osteoporosis in Menopausic women, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 105)
    - Research and Review Committee: Neuropsychological Correlates of Trichotillomania, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 106)
    - Research and Review Committee: The Use of Nimodipine in the Management of Preeclampsia: A Randomized, Controlled Study, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 107)
    - Research and Review Committee: Insulin Sensitivity in Premenstrual Syndrome Patients versus Normal Patients as Measured by the Minimal Model of Frequently Sampled Insulin Glucose Tolerance Test, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 108)
    - Research and Review Committee: The Effects of the Herpes Virus and its Treatment with Acyclovir on Preimplantation Embryos, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 109)
    - Research and Review Committee: Extending Sponsorship Program for Medically Underserved Women, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 110)
    - Research and Review Committee: The Vascular Reactivity of Omental Blood Vessels from Pre-and-Post Menopausal Non-Pregnant Women and Pregnant Women with and without Preeclampsia, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 111)
    - Research and Review Committee: The Effects of Bench Aerobics and Resistance Training on Bone Mineral Density, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 112)
    - Research and Review Committee: The Relationship Between Adult Periodontitis and Osteoporosis in Menopausic Women, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 113)
    - Research and Review Committee: The Museum of Health and Medical Science, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 114)
    - Research and Review Committee: Standing Committee, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 115)
    - Research and Review Committee: Continued Standing Committee, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 116)
    - Research and Review Committee: Free Clinic for Women, "Living and Coping with Breast Cancer", 1993 (Box 18, Folder 117)
    - Research and Review Committee: Psychosocial Factors and Smoking Behavior Change in Women Diagnosed with Coronary Artery Disease, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 118)
- Gifts and Donations, 1980-2014
  Fundraising has been a major thrust of the Women's Fund mission because the organization needs money to implement the other objectives of the mission statement: public education and research support. Included in the Gifts and Donations series are detailed records of ticket sales, corporate contributions, and in-kind donations for administrative support and special events. Folder divisions generally follow original order but were reorganized slightly to maintain chronological groupings.
  - Donations, 1980-1996 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Donations, January-October 1998 (Box 10, Folder 33a)
  - Donations, November 1998-November 1999 (Box 10, Folder 33b)
  - Donations, December 1999 (Box 10, Folder 33c)
  - Donations - Memorial for Martha G. Slaughter, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Donations - In-Kind, 1993-1997 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Donors, 1987-1993 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Contributions Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Contributions Reports, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Contributions, 1979-1996 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Corporate Sponsors and Donations, 1980-1996 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Donations from Women's Fund for HER, 1984-1993 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Grant Solicitations for Support of Women's Fund, 1984-1989 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Donations, Gift Receipts, 2004-2005 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Donations, January 2012 - September 2014 (Box 22, Folder 11-41)
  - Donations Members, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Spring Donations, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Rockin' Donations, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Legacy Sponsors Donations, 2014 (Box 22, Folder 45)
- Printing Samples, 1983-1998
  The Printing Samples Series includes samples of the many invitations, announcements, and programs produced by the Women's Fund over the years. Samples were re-foldered and labeled in original order.
  - 1983 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - 1984 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - 1985 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - 1986 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - 1987 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - 1988 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - 1989 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - 1990 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - 1991 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - 1992 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - 1993 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - 1994 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - 1995 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 1996 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1997 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Publications, 1979-2011
  The Publications series contains materials pertaining to the Women's Fund's publications. Publications include Primer on Women's Health, Health Notes, the Body Works Toolkit, What About Me?: A Girl's Guide to Health, Which Weigh?, a set of historical newsletters, and various one-off fliers and publications.
  - Primer on Women's Health, 1984-1994
    In 1985 the Women's Fund produced a Primer on Women's Health, a free brochure circulated to inform women throughout the Houston community on women's vital health issues. Revised every two years, the Primer promotes the latest in health maintenance information. To date, the Women's Fund, with the help of generous sponsors, has distributed 232,500 copies of the English edition to agencies, corporations, schools, churches, and hospitals. To reach a broader representation of the Houston community, the Women's Fund produced a Primer in Spanish in 1987 and since then the Women's Fund has distributed 106,700 copies of the Spanish edition.
    - 1985 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - 1992 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - 1993 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - 1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - 1998 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - 1999 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - 2001 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Related correspondence, 1984-1994 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Primers "I" (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - "R" Misc. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Postage/Bulk Mail (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Pitney Bowes (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - "U" Misc. (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Seminars (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - "T" Misc. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Richmond Printing (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - "S" Misc. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Sam's Club (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Postage/Reserve Act (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Misc. (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Research and Review Committee (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Research and Review Committee/Good Health (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Petty Cash (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - "P" Misc. (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Ozarka Water (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Office Depot (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Moore Creative (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - "N" Misc. (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - "O" Misc. (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - MIP (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - MinuteMan Press (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Metafile (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - "M" Misc. (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Junior League (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Logix Communications (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Jason's Deli (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Insurance (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - "H" Misc. (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Data Rush (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Barbara Devetski Reimbursements (Box 23, Folder 32)